<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.program.courrier"
       name="Courrier"
       version="0.1.4"
       provider-name="Senufo">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script"
             library="addon.py" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Mail Checker</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Reléve le Courrier</summary>
    <description lang="en">
Courrier is a script for read mail on POP or IMAP servers.

Based on the script and the skin of gmailchecker

Configure server in settings
You can define the max size of messages and a filter to search messages in IMAP server
The text of your message scrolls automatically

At the moment you view message only in text mode and html message are convert in text with Beautilfulsoup and html2text "Aaron Swartz (me@aaronsw.com)" modules.
On bottom you have status line with date and attach file name of the selected message
For IMAP server you can define in SKIN your folder and the flag use for select message
if you have installed service.notfier the script.mail use configuration settings of service.notifier
    </description>

    <description lang="fr">
Courrier est un script pour lire son courrier sur des serveurs POP ou IMAP.
Basé sur le script et le skin de gmailchecker
Configurer le serveur dans le sparamètres
Vous pouvez définir la taille maximale des messages et un filtre pour rechercher des messages dans le serveur IMAP
Le texte de vos messages défile automatiquement
 
Pour le moment le message est affiché en mode texte et le message html est converti en texte avec html2text "Aaron Swartz (me@aaronsw.com)"
Au maximum 3 vignettes d'images attachées peuvent être affichées 
En bas vous avez la ligne d'état avec la date et le(s) nom(s) de(s) fichier(s) attaché(s) du message sélectionné
Pour le serveur IMAP vous pouvez définir votre dossier et l'utilisation d'un filtre pour sélectionner les messages
    </description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <source>https://github.com/senufo/plugin.program.courrier</source>
  </extension>
</addon>
